晚上好
Evening.
喂 喂
Hello. Hello.
- 喂 - 喂
- Hello. -Hello.
- 喂 喂 - 喂
- Hello. Hello. - Hello.
- 喂 - 喂
- Hello. -Hello
喂 喂
Hello. Hello.
把他給我
Give it to me!
- 八塊錢？- 工作進展的很慢
- Eight bucks? - Business is slow.
找一份新的工作 要麼就從這裏搬出去
Get a new business or move out of the neighborhood!
- 快點 - 嗨 帶上那個 豬
- Come on. - Hey, take that! Pig!
把你的手拿開
Get your hands off me!
你們到底什麼時候可以給我 一個答案？
So am I ever gonna get an answer out of you guys?
- 好 長官 - 好
- Well, sir... - Well.
- 恭喜啊 上尉 - 這是什麼 長官？
- Congratulations, captain. - What is it now, chief?
正式的
Oh. It's official.
這裏現在是這個城市最 糟糕的區域
This is now the worst precinct in the entire city.
你看看這個？入室盜竊 佔百分之三十六
Would you look at this? Burglary, up 36 percent.
持械搶劫 佔百分之二十
Armed robbery, up 20 percent.
惡意破壞 佔百分之四十四
Vandalism, up 44 percent.
長官 我認為你查一下的話 入室盜竊至少佔百分之四十八
Sir, I think if you'll check, burglary is up 48 percent.
你 聽到沒有？
There. You hear that?
- 你是誰？- 毛瑟 長官 "Man"裏的"M"
- Who are you? - Mauser, sir. M as in "man"...
- "Sam"裏的A-U-S - 閉嘴坐下 毛瑟
- A-U-S as in "Sam" - Shut up and sit down, Mauser.
- 他沒有問你你的傳記 - 嗯 長官
- He didn't ask for your biography. - E-R, sir.
看看 赫斯特 你預期會怎麼樣？
Look, Hurst, what do you expect?
你縮減了我的預算 減少了我的員工 這叫我怎麼工作啊
You cut my budget, you cut my staff. I got nothing to work with.
看看你周圍 他們都老了 他們累了
Look around! These guys are old. They're tired.
他們是已經減得不能再減的
They just can't cut it anymore.
可能他們需要一個新的上尉 拉賽德
Maybe they need a new captain, Lassard.
市長要結果 你記得這個市長嗎？
The mayor wants results. You remember the mayor?
她想要這個有點進展 你有什麼建議？
She wants something done about this. What do you propose?
你不要在這裏管我的閒事 到市長辦公室去
Take your nose out of my business, go to the mayor's office...
做你應該做的事去
and put it where it usually is.
給你30天的時間來改善這個地區 不然你就出局
You have exactly 3O days to turn this precinct around, or you are out.
你懂了嗎？30天就30天
Do you understand me? Thirty days and that's it!
我至少需要一打的新人
I need at least a dozen new men.
- 可以給你6個人 - 好 謝謝你
- You can have six. - Well, thank you!
你最好可以開始了
You better get started.
不好意思 上尉
Excuse me, captain.
幫我接警察學校 我要和我兄弟說話
Get me the police academy. I wanna speak to my brother.
長官
Sir. Chief.
長官 如果太唐突的話 我很抱歉
Sir, if I may be so bold, I would like to apologize...
關於上尉拉賽德評論有關你 為市長做的事
for Captain Lassard's remark about your nose being up the mayor's...
長官 我有新的想法 來管理好這個地區
Chief, I've got some new ideas on how to run this precinct.
- 哦 我賭你行的 毛瑟 - 長遠計劃 長官
- Oh, I'll bet you do, Mauser. - Long-range plans, sir...
計劃的步驟 部署
planning steps, deployment.
看 長官 這絕對是個領導的問題
See, sir, it's really a question of leadership that works.
拉賽德有30天的時間
Lassard's got 30 days.
如果他搞砸了 這工作就是你的了
If he should blow it, the job is yours.
我完全明白 長官
I fully understand, sir.
毛瑟 你是我見過的最難以置信的 馬屁精
Mauser, you are the most incredible ass-kisser I have ever seen.
非常感謝您的誇獎 長官 我會盡力了
Thank you very much, sir. I do my best.
她一定是出去吃午飯了 警察學校
She must be out to lunch. Police academy.
你好 請找埃裏克 拉賽德
Hello. Eric Lassard, please.
我就是司令官埃裏克 拉賽德
This is Commandant Eric Lassard speaking.
- 埃裏克 我是比特 - 比特？
- Eric, this is Pete. - Pete?
- 我們的兄弟 - 比特
- Your brother. - Pete!
真是非常非常高興你能打電話來 我的小兄弟最近好嗎？
How very, very nice of you to call. How's my baby brother?
還好 埃裏克 實際上 不是很好
Just fine, Eric. Actually, not too good.
哦 怎麼了？
Oh, what's up? Oh, uh...
埃裏克 我碰到一個麻煩
Eric, I've got a problem here.
嗯 我們都有自己的小麻煩的
Yeah, we all have our little problems.
嗯 但是這個很嚴重
Yeah, but this one is serious.
我希望你不是和什麼女孩子 惹上麻煩了
I hope you haven't got a girl into trouble.
不是 我需要的是年輕的男人
No. I need to get my hands on some healthy young men.
我想有些地方你可以去
I guess there are places you could go...
- 某些酒吧啊等等 - 埃裏克 你在說什麼啊？
- Certain bars and so on. - Eric, what are you talking about?
瑪格立特知道這個嗎？
Does Margaret know about this?
埃裏克 我有點麻煩 我要的是一些新兵
Eric, I'm in trouble here, and I need some new recruits.
哦 這樣 那簡單
Oh, well, that's easy.
我們學校有很多很棒的年輕 畢業新兵
We have some very, very fine young graduates here at the academy.
快 快點 快點跑 快點跑
Come on. Come on. Double time. Double time.
撿起來 快點 快點
Pick it up. Move it. Move it.
快 動起來 快走 快走 快走
Come on! Move it! Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
布賴恩 你直接去上課今天
Now, Brian, I want you to go straight to class today.
- 為什麼是我？- 因為是我說的
- Why should I? - Because I said so.
- 老大 - 請注意你的禮貌 先生
- Big deal. - You mind your manners, mister.
- 我不需要 鳥臉 - 你敢 你有麻煩了
- I don't have to, bird face. - That does it. You're in trouble.
哦 我好害怕啊
Oh, I'm just really scared.
- 我可以做什麼 長官？- 好的 警官
- Can I help you, ma'am? - Yes, officer.
我兒子布賴恩上課老是遲到 你可以跟他談談嗎？
My son Brian is always late for school. Could you speak to him?
- 也許給他點懲罰？- 當然 長官
- Perhaps give him a little scare? - Certainly, ma'am.
嗨 布賴恩
Hi, Brian.
快8點了 到時間去學校了
It's almost 0800 hours. Time to deploy for school.
我準備好了就會去的
I'll go when I'm ready.
你已經準備好了 先生
You're ready now, mister.
現在給我走 走 走
Now move it! Move it! Move it!
- 謝謝你 警官 - 沒關係 長官
- Thank you, officer. - No problem, ma'am.
- 沒有比看電視跟好的了 - 我怎麼不知道
-It's really no better than television. - I wouldn't know.
我從來不看電視
I never watch television.
我自己也從來沒有過一部電視機
Personally, I don't even own a television.
肚子餓了 黛安？
Hungry, Diane?
麥克看在上帝分上 送我回家吧
For God's sakes, Michael, just take me home.
* 有人得去做 *
* Somebody's got to do it *
* 這骯髒的工作 *
* It's dirty work *
* 有人需要有人去做 *
* Somebody got Somebody got to do it *
* 有人得去做 *
* Somebody's got to do it *
嗨。你好嗎？
Hi. How are you?
* 我一定是瘋了 我才做這事 *
* I must be crazy To do the things I do *
* 著手解決這一切 加班照顧你 *
* Workin' all this overtime Takin' care of you *
* 一個艱難的任務堅持讓你執行 *
* One tough assignment Keepin' you in line *
* 每次我轉身 你都在我的腦海裏 *
* Every time I turn around You're playin' with my mind *
* 你給我的一切 *
* All the things you put me through *
* 這是一個全職工作 我愛你 *
* It's a full-time job loving you Oh *
* 這骯髒的工作 總要有人做 *
* It's dirty work Somebody's got to do it *
* 這骯髒的工作 *
* It's dirty work *
* 你知道有人有人去做 *
* You know somebody Somebody's got to do it *
- 嗨 提姆 - 親愛的 怎麼了？
- Hey, Tim. - Mahoney, what's happening?
- 你好嗎？- 很好
- How you doing? - All right!
- 聽著 提姆 我有麻煩了 - 是什麼麻煩？
- Listen, Tim, I got a problem. - What's that?
- 有人搞砸了我的工作 - 不
- There's some guy ripping up my beach. - No!
- 真的 - 是誰？
- Yeah. - Who was it?
你
You!
- 聽著 提姆 幫我個忙 - 你明白了
- Listen, Tim. Do me a favor. - You got it!
- 離開這個活兒 - 你還是沒明白
- Get off the beach. - You don't got it!
- 拜託 提姆 做個好孩子 - 沒門 走開 你們
- Come on, Tim, be a good boy. - No way! Out, guys!
再見 小警察
So long, fuzz ball!
* 這骯髒的工作 總要有人做 *
* It's dirty work But somebody's got to do it *
* 這骯髒的工 總要有人做 *
* It's dirty work *
* 你知道有人關心 *
* You know that Somebody's got to care *
* 這骯髒的工作不是一件容易的事 *
* It's dirty work It ain't easy *
* 這骯髒的工作 *
* It's dirty work *
* 你知道有人有人去做 *
* You know somebody Somebody's got to do it *
* 必須這樣做 *
* Got to do it *
決不要耍一個小警察
Never fool with a fuzz ball.
非常榮幸的歡迎你們 還有你 來到第16號地區
It's a real pleasure to welcome you men, and you, to the 16th Precinct.
我的哥們告訴我你是這個學校 畢業的最好的新兵了
My brother tells me you're among the finest ever to graduate the academy.
第16號地區曾經是受到保護的 最好的小區之一
The 16th serves and protects what was once a great neighborhood.
但是很不幸 一幫壞蛋接管了這裏
Unfortunately, a vicious gang has taken over...
他們試圖要控制整個街道
and they're trying to control the streets.
我們不知道他們是誰 從哪裏來的
We don't know who they are or where they come from.
我們只知道他們都是人渣
We do know that they are scum.
我們的職責就是找到他們並 消滅他們
And it is ourjob to find them and bust them.
你們都是在最健全的法律和最新的 技術下受過訓練的
You've all received training in the latest techniques in urban law enforcement.
你們誰有什麼特殊能力是 我不知道的？
Any of you have any special skills that I should know about?
我剛學會如何用一把牛排刀來 做緊急氣管切開手術 長官
I just learned to perform an emergency tracheotomy with a steak knife, sir.
那麼你們這些專業學校畢業的小子要拯救這個地區 對不對？
So these academy rats are gonna save the precinct, right?
嗨 我個人希望 上尉 他們全都栽跟頭
Hey, personally, lieutenant, I hope they fall flat on their asses.
- 你知道這個是可以辦到的 - 什麼意思？
- That could be arranged, you know. - What do you mean?
如果他們失敗了 拉賽德就出局 那麼我就是指揮了
If they fail, Lassard's out. That makes me the captain.
如果我當了上尉 我需要一個新的監督人
If I'm captain, I'll need a new watch commander.
那麼？
So?
- 那麼可以保證他們失敗 - 誰？
- So we make sure they fail. - Who?
- 那些新兵 - 為什麼？
- The new recruits. - Why?
如果他們失敗了 拉賽德就走了 那我就可以來了
If they fail, Lassard is out. I'm in.
我需要一個新的監督人
I'm gonna need somebody to be the new watch commander.
- 哦 - 你知道這個人是誰
- Oh. - And you know who that's gonna be.
- 你？- 你呀 白癡 你
- Who? - You, dickhead. You.
哦
Oh!
哦 好主意
Oh, good idea.
- 你不會玩一副牌的 是嗎？- 嗯 我不打牌的
- Not playing with a full deck, are you? - Oh, I don't play cards.
我要這裏成為本市最棒的 低犯罪率小區
I want this to be the best damn Crime Suppression Unit in the city.
我要我們自豪的挺直腰桿
I want us to stand proud and walk tall.
此外
More than anything...
我還要這裏變成 唔
I want this to be, well...
一個大家庭
one big family...
有一群兄弟和一些姐妹
with a bunch of brothers and little sister...
還有一個偉大的媽媽
and one big mother.
醒醒 我是你的監督人
Wake up! I am your watch commander.
當你想搞糟的時候 你就會搞糟的
When you foul up, and you will foul up...
我要到那裏去寫份報告
I'm gonna be there to write up a report.
三床的報告 你被停職了
Three bad reports, and you're suspended.
- 你叫什麼？- 胡克斯 長官
- What is your name? - Hooks, sir.
- 再說一遍 - 胡克斯
- Say that again. - Hooks.
胡克斯 好 胡克斯警官 我可以看看你的警槍嗎？
Hooks. Well, Officer Hooks, can I please see your service revolver?
不要用槍指著我
Don't point that gun at me.
- 子彈又沒有上膛 - 我怕它會走火
- There's no round in the chamber. - I was afraid it might go off.
哦 天哪 是可能走火的 這個是給胡克斯的
Oh, heavens to be! It might go off! That's one for Hooks.
你在寫報告 看看怎麼樣了？這個絕對簡單
You're on report. See how it works? It's real simple.
這個小組每天分配1000小時
This squad deploys each day at 1000 hours.
正好1000小時
Precisely 1000 hours.
既然你們都只是些生手
Since you boys and girls are only rookies...
你們會被指派一名老手
you will be assigned a veteran officer...
誰來寫一份報告
who will write up a report.
好的 看一下這個任務
Okay, read the assignments.
- 法克勒 - 是 長官
- Fackler! - Yes, sir.
法克勒警官 你右邊的這位先生 是杜雷警官
Officer Fackler. The gentleman on your right is Officer Dooley.
一個好人 他會教你許多東西
A fine man. He's gonna teach you a lot.
- 泰克佈雷？- 是 長官 長官
- Tackleberry? - Yes, sir, sir!
泰克佈雷警官 你是受訓執行摩托車任務的？
Officer Tackleberry. You're trained for motorcycle duty?
是 長官
Yes, sir!
好的 到摩托營去找科克藍德警官
You've got it. Meet Officer Kirkland at the motor pool.
- 多謝 長官 - 好 去吧 耶 走 走 走 走
- Thank you, sir! - Well, get going. Yeah! Go, go, go, go.
- 高塔 - 唷
- Hightower. - Yo!
- 唷？- 唷 長官
- Yo? - Yo, sir.
唷 長官 肯定是從南方來的 是 "是 長官"
Yo, sir! Must be from the South. It's, "Yes, sir."
你是巡邏的 好的 是這樣了
You got foot patrol. Okay, that's it.
- 謝謝你們的耐心 - 那我呢？我沒有一輛車嗎？
- Thank you for your patience. - What about me? Don't I get a car?
"那我呢？我沒有一輛車嗎？"
"What about me, sir? Don't I get a car?"
你不能等到一輛車 你得到一個漂亮的桌子
You don't get a car. You get yourself a nice little desk...
和一把漂亮的椅子 在一個漂亮的辦公室裏 為你美麗的嗓音
with a nice little chair, in a nice little office, for your nice little voice.
- 混蛋 - 是2個
- Asshole. - That's two.
胸圍 48
Chest, 48.
腰圍 44
Waist, 44.
- 褲長 39 - 嗨 我可以要那只長頸鹿嗎？
- Outseam, 39. - Hey, can I have that giraffe?
- 不行 - 哦
- No. - Oh.
我有辦法了
I got an idea.
- 給你一個巧克力怎麼樣？- 給你吧
- How's about for a Snickers bar? - You got it.
謝謝
Oh. Thanks.
總共 48
Overall, 48.
下一個
Next.
請脫下你的槍皮帶
Please take off your gun belt.
胸圍 37
Chest, 37.
腰圍 32 好 轉過去
Waist, 32. Okay, turn around.
請輕點
Please be gentle.
瓊斯 我就知道你要做個壞蛋
Jones, got you figured for an asshole.
我不想被你們取笑 我不想開始
I don't take shit from you people. I'm not gonna start.
不要想 不要說話 不要呼吸 除非我加你這麼做 懂嗎？
Don't think, don't talk, don't breathe unless I tell you. Understand?
- 是 長官 - 好的
- Yes, sir. - All right.
我們已經有點起色了
We're gonna get along just fine.
- 你聽到了嗎？- 沒有 長官
- Did you hear that? - No, sir.
見鬼 我們的一個胎爆了 出去查查你那邊
Doggone it! We got ourselves a flat tire. Get out and check your side.
我的沒事 你的呢？
Mine's okay. How's yours?
沒事 長官
Fine, sir.
那又來了
There it goes again.
警官尤金 泰克佈雷 報告情況 長官
Officer Eugene Tackleberry reporting for duty, sir!
凱絲琳 科克藍德警官
Officer Kathleen Kirkland...
我很高興你沒有打電話給我
and I appreciate you not calling me sir.
好的 帶好你的裝備 科克藍德 我們走
All right. Mount up, Tackleberry. Let's go.
哦 這附近不是很糟糕
Oh, this neighborhood ain't so bad.
你知道怎樣成為一個好警察的秘密嗎？
You know the secret to being a good cop?
你必需先瞭解大家
You gotta get to know the people.
- 唷 你 有火柴嗎？- 有 這兒 拿著吧
- Yo, man, you got a match? - Sure. Here. Keep the pack.
- 謝謝你 - 好 非常好
- Thank you. - Good. Very good!
這就是關鍵 小子 你要先和 大家之間建立信任
That's the idea, son. You gotta build up trust with the people.
然後他們就會尊敬你 知道我的意思了嗎？
Then they'll respect you. Know what I mean?
- 嗯 - 給我2個甜甜圈
- Mm-hm. - Give me two of them glazed doughnuts.
我要一個巧克力的
I'll have a chocolate.
對不起 長官 警官凱裏 馬奧尼 來匯報情況 長官
Excuse me, sir. Officer Carey Mahoney reporting for duty, sir.
馬奧尼警官 很高興你能來這裏走走
Oh, Officer Mahoney. It's nice of you to drop by.
- 我早就想念你了 - 去弄一件新的制服
- I missed you earlier. - Had to get a new uniform.
哦 好 好 不能裸著去見公眾啊 是不是？
Oh, good. Good. We can't face the public naked, can we?
是啊 我們的手銬要掛哪裏？
That's right. Where would we hang our handcuffs?
真可愛 我喜歡一個有幽默感的警官
That's cute. I like an officer with a sense of humor.
我也喜歡你 長官
I like you too, sir.
我真羨慕一個人不怕醜的 這樣用牙線
I admire a guy who's not ashamed to floss.
你知道 長官 口腔衛生是很多 大城市的警察不注意的問題
You know, sir, oral hygiene is something too many big-city cops overlook.
嗯
Hm.
哦 好 好 那你很講衛生啦 哼？
Oh, good. Good. So you like hygiene, huh?
那麼你會喜歡你的新搭檔的:
Then you're gonna like your new partner:
文尼 斯圖曼警官
Officer Vinnie Schtulman.
喂？喂？
Hello? Hello?
- 喂 - 你是誰？
- Hello. - Who is it?
凱裏 馬奧尼 你的新搭檔
Carey Mahoney, your new partner.
- 快進來 快進來 - 謝謝
- Come on in. Come on in. - Thanks.
- 就當這裏是自己家一樣 - 好的 好的
- Make yourself at home. - Alrighty. Alrighty.
- 不要坐那個壞椅子 - 哦 我知道 我看到了 看到了
- Don't sit in the broken chair. - Right. I got it. I saw it. I saw it.
- 你要點什麼早餐嗎？我有雞蛋 - 不
- Would you like breakfast? I got eggs. - No.
我不要了 我遲點再吃 大概是破傷風
I'm fine. I'll get something later. Tetanus shot, maybe.
- 你這裏真是太棒了 - 多謝 是我自己裝飾的
- This is an excellent place you got here. - Thanks. I decorated it myself.
- 嗨 文尼 斯圖曼 - 我手上有花生醬
- Hey! Vinnie Schtulman. - I got peanut butter on my hand.
- 我喜歡花生醬 - 馬奧尼 很高興見到你
- I like peanut butter. - Mahoney. Nice to meet you.
嗨 我吃得很快可以嗎？
Hey, would it be okay if I eat real quick?
- 行 沒事 - 謝謝
- Yeah, go ahead. - Thanks.
除了午餐和晚餐 早餐是一天 裏最重要的一餐了
Next to lunch and dinner, breakfast is the most important meal of the day.
哦 天哪 朋克
Oh, jeez. Bunky.
朋克 我告訴過你多少次了？這是垃圾盒 垃圾盒
Bunky, how many times I gotta tell you? The litter box! The litter box!
- 你肯定你不想要一點嗎？- 我在減肥
- You sure you don't want any? - I'm on a diet.
- 要我把門鎖上嗎？- 不 鄰居可能會來借東西
- Want me to lock the door? - No, neighbors might borrow something.
- 能有個新搭檔真是太好了 - 我正在想這件事
-It's gonna be great having a new partner. - I was thinking about it
我希望盧不會嫉妒
I hope Lou's not jealous.
嗨 你的熏牛肉好了
Hey. Your pastrami's ready.
你有沒有在上面放蛋黃醬？
Did you put the mayo on that?
你很安靜啊 我想你是不喜歡 你的任務
You've been quiet. I take it you don't like your assignment.
- 是的呀 - 是不是因為我是個女的？
- That's affirmative. - Is it because I'm a woman?
我拒絕回答那個問題 這不尊重你的性別
I decline to answer that question out of respect for your gender.
我會照顧好自己的 你自己看管好自己吧
I'll take care of myself. You just cover your own ass.
這個很不錯啊
That's a nice piece.
我正想問問你的裝備
I was referring to your side arm.
- 哦 - 可以嗎？
- Oh. - May I?
當然
Sure.
這是蟒蛇型自動手槍
It's a Colt Python.
- 你用哪種子彈？- 158格令 半沖孔型大威力子彈
- What kind of load do you use? -158-grain semi-wadcutter manstoppers.
智能武器
Sensible weapon.
我用的是一把工廠精確過的 45口徑手槍
I use a factory-accurized Detonics .45 Scoremaster.
他有延長槍桶 後坐力短
It's got the extended barrel, short hammer fall...
我裝的是230格令子彈 裝滿一輪
and I load with 230-grain full patch rounds.
它主要是用在防禦上的
It's primarily for stopping power.
另一方面 如果你想要突破
On the other hand, if you want penetration...
這個 357的子彈可以炸飛 一輛卡車的發動機
the .357 will crack the engine block of a truck.
我可以看到它是多麼有用
I can see where that would be useful.
好啊 觸地得分 好 幹得好
All right. Touchdown! All right! Good job!
- 再給我來一個 - 看那個小小的橄欖球員
- Give me another one. - Look at the little football players.
- 嗨 我們在打球呢 - 過來 小子
- Hey! We're playing ball. - Come on, punk.
- 還給我 - 你想要這球嗎？
- Give it back. - You want the ball?
- 把球給我 - 這兒 去拿吧
- Give me the ball! - Here. Go get it!
哇哦
Whoo!
- 你從沒看過橄欖球嗎？- 嗨 嗨 警察
- You never seen a football? - Hey! Hey, copper!
把球扔給我
Throw me the ball!
快點 你會把球扔回這裏嗎？快 給我
Come on, will you throw it back here? Come on! Give it to me!
- 這不像是個不好的小區 - 這是個很棒的小區
- This is not such a bad neighborhood. - This is a great neighborhood.
- 是哦？- 我是在這裏長的的
- Yeah? - I grew up here.
- 沒門 - 耶
- No way. - Yeah.
- 你？- 這裏的一個小孩
- You? - Little kid here.
小斯圖曼在這裏跑來跑去？
No way. Little Schtulman running around here?
- 你很小嗎？- 那個是我
- You were little? - That was me.
我們應該幫盧從那車上下來 他需要運動
We should get Lou out of the truck. He needs exercise.
- 我們可以遲點幫他 - 凱裏 看這個
- We can get him later. - Carey, look at this.
一根雀巢的脆皮巧克力 幾乎不能去碰它
A Nestle Crunch bar, hardly even been touched.
不足為奇 上面都是螞蟻
No wonder. Got ants all over it.
- 你不會吃的 是嗎？- 你要把它分開？
- You're not gonna eat that, are you? - You wanna split it?
不
No!
不 不 不 你想要我的什麼？出去
No, no, no. What do you want from me? Blood? Get out!
冷靜點 老傢伙
Be cool, old man.
打開保險箱 快點 打開它
Open the safe. Come on. Hurry up. Open it.
快點 把它打開
Come on. Open it up.
- 它總是那樣 - 快一點
- It always does that. - Hurry.
好的
Yeah.
嗯 我搞定了
There. I got it.
嘶嘶聲
Fizzies.
他們沒有多弄點 記得嗎？
They don't make them anymore. Remember?
嘶嘶聲？
Fizzies?
警察
Cops!
蹲下 不然你會死的
Stay down, or you're dead.
- 斯圖曼 有沒有看到一把槍？- 我看到了
- Schtulman, you see a gun? - I saw a gun.
那個是持械搶劫
That's an armed robbery.
- M15小隊呼叫總部 - 這裏是總部
- Unit M-15 to base. - This is base.
我們在卡羅林街302號碰到 搶劫 請指示
We've got a 211 at 302 Caroline Street. Please advise.
- M1 你聽到沒有？- 104 叫他們進去
- M-1, did you read that? -10-4. Tell them to move in.
- 他們要不要等增援來了？- 不 他們不需要增援
- Shouldn't they wait for backup? - No, they don't need a backup.
- 你是不是要助聽器？- 進去 M15小隊
- Do you need a hearing aid? - Move in, M-15.
10 4
1O-4.
快 我們走
Come on. Let's go.
跟著我走底點
Follow me and stay low.
你在這裏嗎？
Are you in here?
文尼 如果他們在這兒 他們不會告訴我們
Vinnie, if they are in here, they're not gonna tell us.
現在 掩護我
Now, cover me.
啊！
Ah!
咳
Whoa!
- 法克勒 - 馬奧尼
- Fackler! - Mahoney!
法克勒
Fackler!
泰克佈雷 別開火
Tackleberry! Hold your fire!
馬奧尼？
Mahoney?
額
An!
高塔警官
Officer Hightower.
- 我認為你以前見過甜心先生？- 甜心先生 我很抱歉
- You met Mr. Sweetchuck, I presume? - Mr. Sweetchuck, I'm so sorry.
我的店 我的店啊
MY store! My store!
我們同時到那裏
We all got here at the same time.
我們不知道我們是
We didn't know that we were--
先生們
Gentlemen...
你已經超越了自己 是嗎？
you've really outdone yourselves, haven't you?
警官們卸下了他們的武器
"Said officers did then discharge their weapons...
公然不顧公眾的安危
with flagrant disregard for public safety...
造成消耗了大約1200輪的彈藥
causing to be expended some 1200 rounds of ammunition.
店的損失總共是76813元
Total damage to the shop: $76,813."
好 我知道你一定非常的憤怒
Well, I know that you must be furious.
在我當差的這些年裏 我還從來沒見過這麼大的損失
In all my years as a police officer, I have never seen such gross negligence.
- 你們還有什麼話要說的？- 長官 我可以說嗎？
- You men have anything to say? - Sir, may I speak?
拉賽德上尉 你的兄弟在學校時教會了我們很多有用的東西
Captain Lassard, your brother taught us many fine things at the academy.
他教導我們一個警察不應該在乎太多 做太大的努力
He taught us that a cop can never care too much or try too hard.
我不知道 長官 那正是我們所做的
I don't know, sir. That's exactly what we did.
- 也許我們過於熱情了 - 過於熱情？
- Perhaps we were a bit overzealous. - Overzealous?
那是1200輪子彈 76813元錢啊
That's 1200 rounds. $76,813.
如果關心是罪 努力又是錯的話
If caring is a crime and trying is a felony...
我想我們都是有罪的
I guess we're all gonna plead guilty.
毛瑟和馬奧尼是對的
Mauser, Mahoney is right.
如果你們也想這些警官一樣努力的話
If your men tried as hard as these officers...
我們就會及時給這幫壞蛋重擊
we'd have this gang licked in no time.
做得好啊 繼續
Good work, men. Keep it up.
體育館見
See you at the gym.
立正 我現在就要點啤酒
Attention! I need beer up here. Now!
好 找點特別的 快啊 大家去買東西吧
Okay, look for specials now! Come on! Shop, everybody!
- 買東西 買東西 - 安全第一
- Shop! Shop! - Safety first!
好啊 快點去啊
Come on! Yeah! Go for it!
你是什麼 一個笨蛋？我是素食者
What are you, a nut? I'm a vegetarian!
水果派 這是我的了
Fruit Loops. They're mine!
夥伴們 夥伴們 過來啊 停止 你 不要像小孩一樣
Guys! Guys! Come on! Stop, man! Act your age!
再見啦
Bye, now.
非常感謝 我發現這裏有 很多很便宜的東西
Thank you very much. I found a lot of really, really nice bargains here.
不好意思 先生 你忘了你的郵票
Excuse me, sir, you forgot your stamps!
先生們 我建議大家一起來舉杯
Gentlemen, I'd like to propose a toast.
至毛瑟上尉 不 不 不
To Lieutenant Mauser. No, no, no--
- 這個地區最大的普斯 - 好的
- Biggest putz of the precinct. - All right.
馬奧尼
Mahoney!
再給我杯啤酒好嗎？
Get me another beer, will you?
- 他是不是有麻煩？- 問的好
- Is he in trouble? - Good question.
- 大頭釘 你怎麼樣啊？- 我想跟你聊聊 馬奧尼
- Tack, what's up? - I need to speak to you, Mahoney.
- 好的 什麼？- 是關於人的天性的
- Okay. What? -It's of a personal nature.
哦 好的 好的 好的
Oh, all right. All right. All right.
我請你喝一杯 怎麼樣？
Let me buy you a drink, all right?
阿特 可以給我杯啤酒 還有牛奶加冰 好嗎？
Art, can I have a beer and milk with ice. Right?
- 好的 那帳單怎麼樣？- 耶 那個沒關係
- Okay. How about a shot? - Yeah, that'll be fine.
嗯 你怎麼樣 泰克？
So, what's up, Tack?
科克藍德 我的搭檔
It's Kirkland. My partner.
哦 是 是 你是個幸運的傢伙 她是個狡猾的人
Oh, yeah. Yeah. You're a lucky guy. She's a fox.
- 那是當然 - 哦 是
- That's affirmative. - Oh, yeah.
關於科克藍德
With regards to Kirkland...
你要什麼東西？
Something you need?
關於科克藍德
With regards to Kirkland...
- 什麼？- 文尼 我
- What? - Well, I...
- 我想我 - 你想什麼？
- I think I'm... - You think what?
- 嗯 我可能 - 泰克 什麼？說出來啊
- Well, I might... - Tack, what? Spell it out.
林肯 歐遜 維克托 愛德華
Lincoln, Ocean, Victor, Edward.
戀愛？尤金 你在戀愛 你這個小壞蛋
Love? Eugene, you're in love! You little devil!
你在戀愛 那太好了
You're in love. That's great!
- 讓我們保持在10到35之間 好嗎？- 哦
- Let's keep this 10-35, okay? - Oh.
當然 當然 在你我之間
Of course, of course. Between you and me.
你和科克藍德？她對你也有吸引力？
You and Kirkland? So she have the hots for you too?
我不知道
I don't know.
我在感情這方面不在行
I'm inexperienced in matters of a romantic nature.
泰克 你以前有交過女朋友嗎
Tack, you've been with women before.
- 嗯 我 - 你以前有一個女朋友
- Well, I-- - You've had one woman before.
- 嗯 不是很對 - 拜託 我看到你和一個女孩逛街的
- Well, not really. - I've seen you walking with girls.
準確的講
To be precise--
你今年28歲 你是一個男人
You're 28 years old. You're a man of the world--
馬奧尼 我是處男
Mahoney, I'm a virgin!
做你自己的事去 不然我要發瘋的
Go about your business, or I'll crack some heads!
- 撲克特 - 哦 上尉 我正在找你
- Proctor! - Oh, lieutenant, I was looking for you.
我有福盧斯在酒吧喝醉的照片 就是你要的那些
I have the pictures of the fruits drunk at the bar, like you asked.
雖然有點合成的
The composition's a little off,
但是長官你可以 清楚的看到那些人是喝醉了
but, sir, you can clearly see those fruits are drunk.
誰要這些人喝醉的照片？我要的是那些新兵在酒吧喝醉的照片
Who asked for fruits drunk at a bar? I asked for new recruits drunk at the bar.
新兵？
Recruits?
上尉 我是學藝術的 我可以幫這個人穿上制服
Lieutenant, I majored in art. I could put a uniform on this guy.
- 看上去有點像高塔 - 你怎麼了 輸了？
- It would look like Hightower. - What are you, losing it?
給我 馬奧尼
Just get me Mahoney.
- 要我保存下來嗎？- 給我 馬奧尼
- Should I save these? - Get me Mahoney!
看這個 看這個 我什麼也沒看見啊 什麼也沒看見
Look at this, look at this. I got nothing here, I got nothing.
- 泰克 你介意嗎？我的生活 - 馬奧尼
- Tack, would you mind? I got a life. - Mahoney!
毛瑟上尉要見你 普諾特
Lieutenant Mauser wants to see you. Pronto!
崩 崩 崩 崩
Bom-bom-bom-bom
什麼時候現在 馬奧尼 你是我的了
Any day now, Mahoney, and your little ass is mine.
你要見我 長官？
You wanted to see me, sir?
你媽媽沒有教過你要先敲門嗎？
Didn't your mother teach you how to knock?
那要看了 長官 我不想變得 太個人了
It depends. Sir, I hope this isn't gonna be too personal.
我聽到你講我的笑話
I heard what you said about my little butt.
我不知道怎樣跟你說 但是我很直接的
I don't know how to break this to you, but I'm straight.
你知道 你很幽默 你知道吧 馬奧尼？
You know, you're very funny, you know that, Mahoney?
每年都會有個新手一位自己 是一位喜劇演員
Every year, we get a rookie who thinks he's a comedian.
好 喜劇演員先生
Well, Mr. Comedian...
看如果你認為這個很好笑
see if you think this is funny.
這是你的新任務
It's your new assignment.
我們要在這裏做些什麼？
What are we supposed to be doing here?
萬一誰的車停了
In case somebody's car stops...
我們從一氧化碳中毒裏救了他們
we save them from carbon monoxide poisoning.
誰來拯救我們呢？
Who's gonna save us?
我想這可能會使你們覺得有點 煩 嗯？
I guess it can get kind of boring, huh?
嗨 盧 盧 接球？這兒
Hey, Lou! Lou, wanna play catch? Here!
去接啊 去接 盧
Go get it. Go get it, Lou.
盧
Lou!
耶 接得好 盧
Yeah. Good catch, Lou.
絲襪
Silk stockings
額
Uh...
對不起？
Excuse me?
- 請問我可以用一下洗手間嗎？- 你要加油嗎？
- Could I use your restroom, please? - You buying gas?
不
No.
那要別處去尿吧
Then pee somewheres else.
- 看 這是一次緊急情況 - 好 帶上鑰匙
- Look, this is a police emergency. - Okay. Take the key.
嗨 不要和那個跑了
Hey, don't run away with that.
通訊是建立一個成功的市民
The key to forming...
守望小組的關鍵
a successful citizen's watch group is communication.
你考慮一下這個地區
I want you to think of this precinct...
作為一個小型通訊網絡的中心
as the hub of a miniature communications network...
從你們家延展到每個警官 每時每刻
stretching from each of your homes to every officer, on duty and very dirty.
- 盧 讓我們弄點吃的 - 誰有阿司匹林嗎？
- Lou, let's get something to eat. - Anybody got any aspirin?
我頭疼 沒完沒了
I've got a headache that's not gonna quit.
哦 好 看這個 這裏 是瓊斯 男孩
Oh, well, look at this, here. It's the Jones Boys.
好傢伙 馬奧尼
Holy mackerel there, Mahoney.
你做了什麼 吞了一輛公共汽車？
What did you do, suck up a bus?
盧 你不喜歡我 我也不在乎你
Lou, you don't like me, and I'm not crazy about you.
斯圖曼 你把他帶走
Schtulman, you keep him away from me.
如果你需要我 我在洗澡
I'll be in the shower if you need me.
嗨 馬奧尼 幫我個忙
Hey, Mahoney, do me a favor.
不停的搖這東西 我好修我的頭盔
Keep shaking this stuff so I can fix my helmet.
- 你做了什麼 弄好它了？- 耶 我要把它弄上去
- What did you do, crack it? - Yeah, I gotta put that on it.
- 一種膠水？- 這個環癢樹脂
- Some sort of a glue? - It's epoxy resin.
- 你是說 當它變硬的時候 它 - 它會變成塑料
- You mean, when it hardens, it -it turns into plastic.
- 要多長時間？- 幾秒鐘
- How long does it take? - A few seconds.
- 那它可以持續多久？- 幾年
- How long does it last? - A few years.
* 某一天 *
* And someday *
* 我要成為隊長 *
* I'm gonna be captain *
* 和每一個新秀將在臣服於他的膝下 *
* And every rookie will go down on his knee *
* 他們將被奴隸 只是為了我 *
* And they'll be nothing but slaves just for me *
* 是的 他們將被奴隸只是為了我 *
* Yeah, they will be slaves just for me *
* 是的 寶貝 奴隸的奴隸 我說 是的 *
* Yeah, baby, slaves Slaves, I said, yeah *
* 他們會喊"毛瑟 隊長" *
* And they'll say "Captain Mauser" *
* 呦 呦 哦 是的 *
* Yowza, yowza Oh, yeah *
* 哦 是的 *
* Oh, yeah Oh *
* 哦 *
* Oh *
嗨
Hey.
Hey!
嗨 等等
Hey! Wait a minute!
我的手粘在了我的頭上 嗨 邊上有人嗎？
My hand got stuck to my head! Hey, who's fooling around?
怎麼了？啊
What the fuck? Okay.
嗨 不要杵在旁邊 小子
Okay. Let's not fool around, fellas.
是我 我沒有在開玩笑
It's me, and I'm not kidding around.
誰幫我幫這個從我頭髮上弄開 是你嗎 斯圖曼？
I want someone to take this out of my hair! Is that you, Schtulman?
我沒有在開玩笑 快 幫幫我
I'm not kidding around! Now, give me a hand.
這不好笑 那很幼稚 好好 把它剪了
That ain't funny. That's very childish. All right, cut it out!
你像個孩子 小孩子
You're acting like children. Children!
嗨 誰 把我的手從我的頭上拿開
Now, somebody, just pull my hands out off my head now!
誰在這裏嗎？
Who's in here?
是誰？是誰？我會記住那聲音的
Who's that? Who's that? I'll remember that voice.
如果我記起那聲音 你們死定了
If I remember that voice, you guys are dead.
死 死定了 去死 這兒有人嗎？好 這是誰？
Dead! D-E-A-D! Dead! ls somebody here? Okay, who is this?
好的 盧 哦 盧 過來 不 盧 不要咬我那裏 盧
All right, Lou. Come on, Lou. No, Lou, don't bite me there. Lou.
盧 求你了 盧 盧 求你了 盧
Lou. Please, Lou. Lou, please. Lou.
噢 不 噢 不 盧 盧 好孩子 盧
Oh, no. Oh, no, Lou. Lou. Good dog, Lou.
喔 不 喔 不 盧 不要 盧
Oh, no! Oh, no, Lou! No, Lou!
好了 把門打開 嗨 你 我不是在開玩笑
All right. Open that door now! Hey, you. I'm not kidding here!
好好
Well...
怎麼啊 你從來沒看過別人洗頭嗎？
What's the matter, you never saw a man wash his hair before?
哦
Oh.
拉賽德上尉
Captain Lassard.
如果你需要我 我在房裏
I'll be in my room if you need me.
撲克特
Proctor!
- 哦 這剛剛好 - 嗯？
- Oh, this is gonna be just fine. - Yeah?
等等 這裏剪一下 讓我用大拇指來弄
Wait, one snip here. Let me get by the thumb.
- 嗯？- 哦 那－那看上非常自然
- Yeah? - Oh, that's-- That looks very natural.
- 看上去還好吧？- 非常非常好
- Looks okay? - It's very, very good.
我想你幾乎分不出來
I don't think you'll be able to tell the difference.
我跟你打賭這都是馬奧尼的責任
I'll bet you anything it was Mahoney responsible for this.
我過去後 我把它再弄得好一點
After I'm through, just let me shape this a little bit...
我相信你們會很高興的我們在這裏
and I think you're gonna really be happy with what we've got here.
- 嗯？讓我看看 - 好
- Yeah? Let me see it. - Sure.
好的
Okay.
嗯？嗯？
Huh? Huh?
看這兒後面 這裏上面
Just look at it in the back here. Look at it over here.
給我面鏡子 勞駕？
Could I have the mirror, please?
好
Sure.
上尉？
Lieutenant?
長官？
Sir?
不 不 不 弄個假髮
No, no, no. We'll get a wig.
你今天沒有看到這個國家藝術的 假髮嗎 長官？
Have you seen the state-of-the-art in wigs today, sir?
你再說什麼啊？
What the hell are you talking about?
我該怎麼辦？
What am I gonna do about this?
- 嗨 你在幹嗎？- 走開 女士 求你了？
- Hey, what you doing? - Leave me alone, lady, please?
好吧
Well...
這就是我所期待的嗎
This is just what I've been looking for.
- 我不擔心你這樣 - 振作 振作
- I'm not afraid of you punks. - Come on, man. Come on!
- 在這兒 - 你要去哪？
- Right here. - Where are you going?
- 我哪也不去 - 不要這樣 我會幫你的
- I ain't going nowhere. - Come on, I'll take you all on.
過來 我需要你 我不怕偷錢包的小偷
Come on, I want you. I'm not afraid of a wallet thief.
- 現在就你和我 - 你和我
- Now it's just you and me. - You and me.
好的 過來 過來
Okay, come on. Come on.
過來 我說得累了 廢物
Come on. I'm tired of talking to you, punk.
我想跳舞 我想把我的手搭在你身上
I wanna dance. I wanna get my hands on you.
也 你現在想和我說話了？好 讓我看看
Yeah. You ready to talk to me now? Come on. Show me.
教我
Teach me.
好 一起來 放我下來
Okay, one at a time. Put me down!
- 快點 放我下來 - 哦 我們會放你下來的
- Come on, put me down. - Oh, we'll put you down, all right.
正在這個時候
At this point in time...
你正是一個不懷好意的惡作劇 的目標
yours truly was the object of a malicious prank.
現在
Now...
這裏有誰可以告訴我這是怎麼 發生的？
can anybody in here tell me how this happened?
我可以 長官 如果你不制止它的話 你就是瞎了眼了
I can, sir. And if you don't stop that, you could go blind.
你認為那很好笑 是嗎 馬奧尼
You think that's funny, don't you, Mahoney?
好 你正在寫報告 把他寫進去
Well, you're on report. Put him on report.
你們不要離開這房間 直到找到發生了什麼
We are not gonna leave this room until we find out what happened.
- 發生了什麼？- 這兒怎麼了？
- What happened? - What's going on here?
沒什麼 我在教訓他們
Nothing. I was just reprimanding the men.
- 和你的教訓見鬼去吧 - 你不明白
- To hell with your reprimands. - You don't understand.
- 閉嘴 我有話要說 - 你看看我的手？
- Shut up, I have something to say. - Would you take a look at my hands?
我認為那是個人衛生的問題
I think that's a matter of personal hygiene.
- 我講的是公眾安全 - 是
- I am talking about public safety. - Yes, sir.
大家聽著 這是認真的
Now listen up, everybody. This is serious.
我們要做點什麼了
We've gotta do something.
這是一場戰爭 現在 我們還沒有開始
This is war! Now, we didn't start it...
我們就要結束了
but we are going to finish it.
我不介意我們要花更多的時間
I don't care if we work time and a half...
我不介意如果要花雙倍的時間
I don't care if we have to work double time...
但是記住我的話 我們要釘死 這些小阿飛 從現在開始
but mark my words, we are gonna nail these punks, starting now!
- 我們會做到的 - 耶
- We can get them! - Yeah!
讓他們去死吧
Let's kick ass!
- 不許動 - 不許動
- Freeze! - Freeze!
把他們銬起來
Cuff them.
不行 我忘帶手銬了 它們在車上
I can't. I forgot my cuffs. They're on the bike.
沒關係
No problem.
嗨 嗨 不好意思 我討厭打斷別人 我可以去參加婚禮嗎？
Hey, hey. Excuse me. I hate to interrupt, but can I go to the wedding?
我意思是 我準備了禮物 看 遠處 唔？
I mean, I've got a gift. Look. Remote. Huh?
對不起
Excuse me.
- 我想你不應該那樣做 - 你會怎麼辦？
- I don't think you should be doing that. - What you gonna do about it?
- 我必須逮捕你 - 你不要用那個
- I have to arrest you or something. - You don't wanna use that.
看 我是認真的 那是我的
Look, I'm serious. That's my--
哦 對不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦 我不知道
Oh, I didn't know--
賽得不喜歡你不付錢
Zed don't like when you miss payments.
你遲到了
You're late.
嗨
Hey!
那是我的蔬菜商
That's my greengrocer.
去巡邏你的地方 警官
Walk your beat, cop.
- 他認為他是布魯斯 李 - 你要打賭嗎？
- He thinks he's Bruce Lee. - You wanna bet?
去你的
Damn you.
想打架嗎 唔？
Wanna fight, huh?
打啊
Fight me!
他很棒
He's very good.
我喜歡
I like this.
哦 不是西蘭花
Oh! Not on broccoli!
哦 不是花菜
Oh! Not on cauliflower!
- 嗨 嗨 - 甜心
- Hey, hey. - Sweetchuck!
你去哪裏？
Where you going, man?
過來 媽媽
Come on, mother.
過來 過來 這裏
Come on! Come on back here, man!
- 過來 他在這裏 - 他在我們周圍
- Come, he ran in here! - We got him surrounded!
嗨
Hey.
好 好的 好的 我們會去的
Right. Okay, okay. We'll be right there.
在藍牡蠣酒吧有一場火拚 我們要不要派特種部隊？
There's a huge fight at the Blue Oyster Bar. Should we send the SWAT team?
- 不 - 真的？
- No. - No?
你派馬奧尼去
You send Mahoney in.
M 15 藍牡蠣酒吧有群毆
M-15, a 415 in progress at the Blue Oyster Bar.
- 藍牡蠣？- 我知道那裏 等一下
- Blue Oyster? - I'll get the address. Hold on.
- 藍牡蠣酒吧在 - 科萬大街621號
- The Blue Oyster Bar is - 621 Cowan Avenue.
我去了
I'm going in.
出來了
Coming out!
嗨 高塔
Hey, Hightower.
這兒看上去很糟
Uh... Looks pretty bad in there.
我進去了
I'm going in.
哦 不 不 不 高塔 別進去
Oh, no, no, no. Hightower, don't go in there.
你會殺了你自己的 高塔
He's gonna get himself killed. Hightower!
把這個放上卡車 我馬上回來
Put these in the truck. I'll be right back.
他馬上就回來
He'll be right back.
你有權利保持沉默 有權找法庭指定的律師
You have the right to remain silent. The right to a court-appointed attorney.
你有權利唱藍調 你有權看有線電視
You have the right to sing the blues. You have the right to cable TV.
你有權轉租
You have the right to sublet.
你有權粉刷這牆壁 顏色不要太亮
You have the right to paint the walls. No loud colors.
高塔 太感謝你了
Hightower. Thanks a lot, man.
隨時效勞
Anytime.
你們都好嗎
Y'all be good, now.
- 不好意思 - 怎麼了
- Excuse me. - Yeah.
我可以要你的簽一下這個嗎？
Could I have your signature?
- 好的 要簽什麼？- 授權體腔調查
- Sure. What do you got? - Authorization for a body cavity search.
聽著 你們每個人 當然還有你
Listen, each and every one of you men, and you too, of course...
功勞當之無愧
deserve real congratulations.
這是警界的一段佳話 真的
That's a damn fine piece of police work. Really.
我想今天你們都感到有所不同
I think you'll feel the difference today.
整個地區正為之興奮
The whole neighborhood is excited about this.
是真的 撲克特
Really. Proctor!
- 我告訴你 這裏警戒結束後 - 太棒了
- When this watch is over... - Yeah.
我們去酒吧好好的喝一杯
we'll go to the Club & Cuff. Drinks on me.
上尉 赫斯特首長電話
Captain, Chief Hurst is on the phone.
- 我們要走了 長官 - 不 不 不 這是給你的 唔？
- We'll leave you alone, sir. - No, no, no. This is for you too, huh?
拉賽德
Lassard.
是 長官
Yes, sir.
逮捕42人 長官 是
Forty-two arrests, sir. Yes.
好的 我告訴過你這些新兵可以 幹好的 長官
Well, I told you these young recruits could take care of the job, sir.
毛瑟帶來了更多的好消息 你等一下？
Mm-hm. Here comes Mauser with more good news. Can you hold on?
我恐怕我們要失去控制權了
I'm afraid we had to drop most of the charges.
看上去我們要失去控制權了？
It appears we had to drop most of the charges?
不合適的拘捕程序
Improper arrest procedures.
- 沒有必要動用武力 長官 - "沒有必要使用武力"？
- Unnecessary use of force, sir. - "Unnecessary use of force"?
我們必須把那些囚犯放了
We had to release the prisoners.
對不起給你們帶來壞消息 還有什麼事？
Sorry to be the bearer of bad news. Will there be anything else?
沒了 我只想一個人待會
I'm really sorry. No, I just wanna be alone.
不正當使用武力？
Unnecessary use of force?!
他們在說什麼？他們是怎麼做事的？
What are they talking about? How are they supposed to do the job?
馬奧尼
Mahoney.
毛瑟
Mauser...
我知道你在幹嗎
I know what you're doing.
那麼你是不是要對我好點？
Then you better be nice to me, huh?
因為馬上我又要管理這裏了
Because I'm gonna be in charge here soon.
嗯 嗯 嗯
Huh? Huh? Huh.
耶 我稍後會弄的
Yeah, I'll get to that later.
我很好
I'm all right.
我正在試
I'm trying.
泰克
Tack!
泰克 為什麼這樣打扮？你看上去不錯
Tack, why all dressed up? You look great.
- 我和科克藍得有個約會 - 你小子
- I got a date with Kirkland. - You little
第一次約會 嗯？不錯 不錯
Your first date, huh? Good going, good going.
- 那是什麼 古龍香水？- 不是 是槍的潤滑油
- What you got there, cologne? - No. It's gun oil.
- 馬奧尼在哪兒？- 這兒
- Where's Mahoney? - Here.
嗨 馬奧尼？有人要找你
Hey, Mahoney? Somebody here to see you.
- 你是馬奧尼？- 是的
- You Mahoney? - Yeah.
- 我來自BCS - BCS？
- I'm here for the BCS. - BCS?
- 體腔調查 - 哦 好 好 好
- Body cavity search. - Oh, right, right, right.
他在哪裏？
Where is he?
都出去了
Everybody out.
讓我們離開這裏
Let's get out of here.
你在幹嗎？等一下
Hey! What are you doing? Wait a minute!
- 閉嘴 - 你在幹嗎？
- Shut him up. - What are you doing?
休息一下 我們馬上就會有起色的
Now, just relax, and we'll get along fine.
我們稍後再談
We'll talk later.
你好 泰克佈雷
Hello, Tackleberry.
科克藍得
Kirkland.
你看上去很漂亮啊
You look very nice.
允許我也回敬你一下
Permit me to respond in kind.
我以前從來沒看過你穿公務員服
I've never seen you in civilian attire before.
- 失望嗎？- 哦 不是
- Disappointed? - Oh, negative.
- 你的？- 哦 不
- And you? - Oh, no.
好 快7點了 我們該走了
Well, almost 1900 hours. Guess we better go.
對
Right.
這兒
Here.
這是什麼？
What's this?
是耳朵手銬 我特地為你做的
They're ear cuffs. I had them made just for you.
禮物
Gift.
晚安 泰克佈雷
Good night, Tackleberry.
晚安 科克藍得
Good night, Kirkland.
- 泰克佈雷？- 是？
- Tackleberry? - Yes?
我愛你
I love you.
Ditto.
- 哦 尤金 - 哦 凱絲琳
- Oh, Eugene. - Oh, Kathleen.
尤金
Eugene.
哦 尤金
Oh, Eugene!
晚上好
Good evening.
好 請
Oh, excuse, please.
生日快樂 皮特
Happy birthday, Pete.
不是我生日 艾瑞克
It's not my birthday, Eric.
那些廢話有必要嗎？
Is all that crap necessary?
- 你看上去有點急 皮特 - 不 我很好
- You seem a little edgy, Pete. - No, I'm fine.
- 你要筷子還是叉子？- 事情運轉的如何？
- You want chopstick or fork? - How are things at work?
糟透了
Awful.
如果我不快點做好的話 我會失去工作
If I don't do something quick, I'm out of a job.
他們說我太老了
They're saying I'm too old.
他們說我失敗了
They're saying I'm losing it.
他們說我有妄想癥
They're saying that I'm paranoid.
他們都要來弄我 愛瑞克
They're all out to get me, Eric.
嗨 嗨 嗨 嗨
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
- 放鬆 - 啊
- Try to relax. - Ah!
我很抱歉 只是疲勞過渡
I'm sorry. It's just the strain, that's all.
你這個笨蛋
You stupid bastard!
對不起
Excuse me.
你為什麼要這樣對我？
Why are you doing this to me?
- 誰？- 你
- Who? - You!
那些你給我的新兵
And those rookies you sent me.
他們做的就是攪和
All they can do is screw up.
現在這個地區開始反對我們 他們從四面八方都針對我
The neighborhood is turning against us. They're coming at me from all directions.
那很正常
That would be normal.
你為什麼不做點什麼？
Why don't you do something?
- 比如說？- 嗯
- Like what? - Well...
做點事使這個地區安定
something to reassure the neighborhood.
為這個地區做個特殊的 警民秀
A special show of police involvement for the neighborhood.
街道展覽
A street fair.
愛瑞克 這個主意太棒了
Eric, that's a brilliant idea.
這是幹什麼的？
What's a big brother for?
- 這條魚熟了 - 哦 你要炒一下嗎？
- This fish is boiling. - Oh, you want stir-fry?
慢慢來 太簡單了 就算是四分位也會做
Step right up! It's so simple even a quarterback can do it.
- 你看上去像個四分位 - 我？
- You look like a quarterback. - Me?
- 是啊 - 你拿一下？
- Yeah. - Hold this?
幫你拿著棉花糖 快
I'll hold your cotton candy.
我知道你行的 快點
I know you can do it. Come on.
從你的肩上拿起來
Get it up on your shoulder.
謝謝你 市長夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Mayor.
現在這個清掃將會成為 新的精神標誌
Now, this broom is just a symbol of the new spirit...
就是要清掃整個地區範圍
that's sweeping across our neighborhood.
所以 市長夫人 也許你會加入我們的
And so, Mrs. Mayor, perhaps you'll join with me...
為街區清掃犯罪的活動
in sweeping the crime off our streets for good.
- 這兒在幹什麼？- 警察們在做展覽
- What's going on here? - Cops are having a fair.
- 為了什麼？- 他們試圖融資
- What for? - They're trying to raise money...
來打掃這個地區
to clean up the neighborhood.
那正是太好了
That's awful nice of them.
他們會安排比賽和獎勵嗎？
Are they gonna have games and prizes and rides?
是
Yeah!
- 他們有大的宣傳車嗎？- 他們有一輛很大的
- Are they gonna have a Ferris wheel? - They got a big one.
我討厭宣傳車
Ah! I hate Ferris wheels!
- 我的胃不好 我感到不舒服 - 額
- I got a bad stomach. Make me sick. - Aw...
- 你不一定要坐上去 - 不
- You don't have to ride on it. - No!
- 好的 如果你和我一起我會繼續做 - 好的
- Well, I'll go on it if you go on with me. - Okay.
- 讓我們去玩吧 - 好
- Let's go have some fun. - Yeah!
這是故意傷害
It's mayhem.
- 喂 你是市長嗎？- 是 我是
- Hi, are you the mayor? - Yes. Yes, I am.
- 我投了你的票 - 哦 你正是太好了
- I voted for you. - Oh, that was very nice of you.
- 我知道我是受命投票的 - 長官 這不像你
- I know when I'm whipped. - Sir, that's not like you.
- 誰是接管這裏的？別告訴我是 - 馬奧尼
- Who's taking over? Don't tell me. - Mahoney.
毛瑟上尉找你在集合室 現在
Captain Mauser wants to see you in the squad room. Now.
從這一刻開始 我是這個地區 的執行指揮官
From this moment on, I am the de facto commander of this precinct.
我的名字是毛瑟上尉 上尉
My name is Captain Mauser. Captain.
星期四以後
On Thursday last...
你就會成為令人厭惡的個人 攻擊的目標
yours truly was the object of a disgusting personal attack.
我想要幾個名字
And I would like to have some names.
就幾個名字
Just some names.
好的
Okay.
照你的方法 但是我會中止 一些個別的
Have it your way. But I will suspend every single one of you!
長官
Sir.
我做了
I did it.
馬奧尼
Mahoney.
馬奧尼？
Mahoney?
- 你認為我是一個怎麼樣的小丑？- 雜耍小丑？
- What kind of clown do you think I am? - A juggling clown?
- 你被停職了 不確定 坐下 - 你不能做這個
- You're suspended. indefinitely! Sit down! - You can't do that.
- 你停他職 停我職 - 我很榮幸
- What? - You suspend him, you suspend me.
坐下 爛人
My pleasure. Sit down, smelly.
我們不知道他們是從哪裏來的 他們躲在那裏
We don't know where they come from, where they hide out.
我們甚至不知道誰是他們的領導者
We don't even know who their leader is.
- 上帝 我會喜歡去釘住那些傢伙嗎 - 我想要我的工作
- God, would I like to nail that bunch. - I would love to get my job back.
我看到布拉特會怎麼做
I say we do what Baretta would do.
布拉特？
Baretta?
- 什麼？- 從事簡單活動
- What? - Go undercover.
滲透到黑幫李 取得他們的信任
Infiltrate the gang. Get their confidence.
- 斯圖曼 - 你想你可以做嗎？
- Schtulman. - You think you could do that?
不
No.
不是他可以
But he could.
- 他是對的 - 不
- He's right. - No.
你夠年輕
You're young enough.
該死 你甚至像一個小馬匹精
Hell, you even look like one of the little creeps.
- 他在說一個電視節目 - 馬奧尼 真相在這裏
- He's talking about a television show. - Mahoney, here's the deal.
現在 我不能付你工資 甚至開支也不能給你
Now, I can't pay you a salary, can't even give you expenses.
如果你自己身陷泥潭的話 我可不會拉你出來
If you get yourself in a jam, I might not be able to bail you out.
- 可能很危險 - 你可能會死
- Could be dangerous. - You could get killed.
他說得對
He's right.
聽上去非常誘人
Sounds awfully tempting.
走開 他會叫你回去
Get out of there! He'll call you back!
我說 他會叫你回去
I said, he'll call you back!
- 嗨 你 嗨 你 你在幹什麼？- 啊
- Hey, man! Hey, man, what you doing? - Ah!
- 沒什麼 - 你為什麼要那樣對電話？
- Nothing. - Why'd you mess up the phone?
我喜歡 不要坐那麼近
I felt like it. Don't sit so close!
- 我是弗蘭克 這是我的人魔酒 - 他們叫你什麼？
- I'm Flacko. This is my man Mojo. - What do they call you, man?
- 笨蛋 笨蛋 - 我和魔酒 我們和卑鄙的人在一起
- Jughead!Jughead! - Me and Mojo, we're with the Scullions.
- 誰和你在一起？- 阿齊斯 阿齊斯
- Who do you run with? - The Archies. The Archies.
- 我從沒聽說過阿齊斯 - 曾經是福特帕克斯
- I ain't never heard of no Archies. - Used to be the Fudpuckers.
- 哦 我知道一點關於福特帕克斯 - 不要壓你的運氣
- Yeah, I think I know some Fudpuckers. - Don't press your luck!
- 嗨 你該和我們在一起 - 嗯 好？為什麼？
- Hey, you should be with us. - Oh, yeah? Why?
- 因為我們是最差的 - 你們才是最差的
- Because we the baddest. - You the baddest.
- 我這樣才能成為一顆青蔥？- 是卑鄙的人 不是青蔥
- How do I get to be a Scallion? - Scullion, not Scallion.
有什麼區別？你很幸運和我坐在一起
What's the difference? You're lucky you're sitting with me.
別擔心 我們會讓你進來
We get you in.
有人來了 小心你的腳 他要踩過去
Here comes the Man. Watch your feet, he's gonna run them over.
好 我的 我的
Well, my, my.
喂 你 你們怎麼樣？
Hello. What are you boys up to, huh?
知道什麼是破壞公物嗎？
Know anything about destruction of property?
- 嗨 我們什麼也沒做 - 哦 你們沒有？哦 看那兒
- Man, we ain't done nothing. - Oh, you ain't? Oh, my, look at that.
叫他們靠牆站 還有你 奇科
Put them against the wall. You too, chico.
快 爬過來 把腿分開
Come on, get over there! Spread your legs!
快的
Come on!
你在做什麼啊？快點 分開他們
What do you think you're doing? Come on! Spread them!
別的 別的 閉嘴 出來
Don't move! Don't move! Shut up! Get out of the car.
到這裏來 扔掉你的槍 我們現在來放鬆一下
Come over here. Toss out your gun. Now we're gonna have a little fun.
知道我的意思嗎？放鬆一下 現在你分開他們 分開他們
Know what I mean? A little fun. Now you spread them. You spread them.
- 踢他 耶 踢他 - 哦
- Now kick him. Yeah, kick him. - Ow!
你喜歡嗎？再踢一次 重一點
You like that? Kick him again. And harder.
- 你瘋了 - 你喜歡嗎？拿著 拿著 嗨 瓊斯
- You're crazy. - You like that? Hold it. Hey, Jones.
就是這個 就是這個 好的 離開那輛車
That's it, that's it, that's it. All right. Now get away from the car.
離開那輛車
Get away from the car.
他是誰？他是在罵我們嗎？也許我們也要回敬他
Who's this guy? This guy giving us lip? Maybe we should give him a little lip.
你喜歡嗎？再來一點？
You like that? How about some more?
嗨 出來 出來
Hey, get out of here. Get out of here.
希望你們還好 長官 你怎麼看？
Hope you're all right, sir. What do you think?
漂亮 寶貝
Beautiful, baby.
- 這個小女孩 過來 祖恩 - 這是我弟弟布得
- There's the little girl. Come, June. - This is my big brother, Bud.
- 嘿 媽媽 - 嘿 布得
- Hi, Mom. - Hi, Bud.
- 嘿 小姑娘 - 哦 爸爸
- Hi, little girl. - Daddy!
- 你要離開爸爸嗎？- 這是尤金
- So you're gonna leave Daddy? - This is Eugene.
嗨 泰克佈雷
Hi, Tackleberry.
- 做得好 - 我最好看看烤得怎樣
- Good grip. - I better check the roast.
好 看看烤肉 甜心
Yeah, check the roast, sweetheart!
嗨 過來 坐下
Hey, come on. Sit down.
嗯
Uh-huh.
我的小妹妹告訴我 你們在自我防禦
My little girl here tells me that you're into self-defense.
- 很正確 長官 - 好 好的
- That's quite correct, sir. - Yeah, well...
1944年我曾經是南太平洋的海軍修建營成員
I was in the South Pacific back in '44, in the Seabees.
爸爸是海軍修建營中量級冠軍
Daddy was middleweight champion in the Seabees.
我以前很會拳擊 我的兒子也是
I used to be pretty good at boxing, but my boy is pretty good too.
他是高中冠軍隊的
He was on the high school championship team.
- 哼？- 好吧
- Huh? - Yeah.
- 但是我可以打敗他 對嗎？- 我不知道 爸爸 別擔心
- But I can still take him, right? - I don't know, Dad. Take it easy.
- 不要這樣 - 我不認為 爸爸
- Come on! - I don't think so, Dad.
快 快
Come on. Come on.
- 哦 你是對的 爸爸？- 嗨 不錯 是吧？
- Oh, you all right, Dad? - Hey, pretty good, huh?
- 對不起孩子？還好嗎？- 還好
- I'm sorry, kid, huh? It's all right, huh? -It's all right.
好
Good!
哦 哦 哦
Oh! Oh. Oh.
- 你還好吧？- 好？那是
- Are you all right? - Good, huh? That was...
你們不要玩了 過來吃飯 晚飯準備好了
You boys stop that foolishness and come to the table. Dinner's ready!
當他們倆開始的時候 他們只是兩個小孩
When these two start at it, they're just a couple of kids.
你說什麼？去吃點東西？
What do you say? Go have some chow, huh?
甜的嗎？
Aren't they sweet?
隊長 你是否可以給他錄音 越高越好
Captain, if you could tape this on him as high as you can.
- 你哪裏弄來的這個？- 我做的
- Where did you get this thing? - I built it.
- 為什麼他說"麥克風先生"？- 沒問題 我改動了少少
- Why does it say "Mr. Microphone"? -It's okay. I made a few modifications.
好的 長官 長官 有點緊
All right, okay. Sir! Sir, it's a little tight.
- 啊 - 對不起 好 等等
- Ah! - Sorry. Okay, hold on.
好了 看 今晚他們帶我去見黑幫 的首領 老大
Look. Tonight, they're taking me to meet the leader of the gang, the head guy.
不錯 只要這個開著 我們就可以聽到每個字 是嗎？
That's good. As long as this is on, we'll hear every word, right?
- 對 - 幫我一個忙 也算幫你自己
- Right. - Do me a favor, and yourself.
給我一個提示然後該幹嗎幹嗎去
Just try to drop a hint now and then as to where you are...
那麼我們就可以跟蹤你了 好嗎？
so we can sort of keep track of you, okay?
- 長官？- 怎麼
- Sir? - Yeah.
- 你肯定這能行嗎？- 不要擔心了？
- You sure this is gonna work? - Will you stop worrying?
馬伕雷鞦韆 是家庭式的
Mumphrey swings. And it's a home run!
是偶爾的嗎 輕輕的推一下
Does that every once in a while. Just give it a tap.
- 嗨 - 好的
- Hey! - All right.
好的 嗨 該你了
All right. Hey, it's your shot.
對不起 嗨 好車啊
Sorry. Hey, hey, great car.
- 哪裏買的？- 進來
- Where'd you buy it? - Get in.
- 好 - 坐後面
- All right. - In the back.
- 後面 - 快點 我們走
- In the back. - Come on, let's go.
嗨 很熱啊 把你的外套脫了
Hey, man, it's hot. Take off your coat.
不 不 不 我很好 我很好
No, no, no. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- 我喜歡熱 - 靠 靠
- I like hot. - Damn. Damn!
我們去哪？
Where we going?
你自己去想我是知道的
That's for me to know, you to find out.
好 好 我猜弗蘭克是對的 是
Right, right. I just like to drive. Right.
- 等你見到賽得後 - 賽得？
- Wait until you meet Zed. - Zed?
- 是 他是好人 - 他不好
- He's the man. - He's bad.
嗨 他是最好的
Hey, he's the best.
- 馬奧尼 跟我說 - 長官 他聽不到你
- Mahoney, talk to me. - Sir, he can't hear you.
我知道 斯圖曼
I know that, Schtulman.
嗨 你要去南部嗎？
Hey, are we going south?
因為南部有更多的敵人
Because I got a lot of enemies down South.
耶 好
Yeah, man. Yeah, man.
我喜歡 我喜歡 我不知道我在哪裏 我喜歡
I like it, man. I like it. I don't know where I am. I like it.
哎 我們有新朋友了 朋友
Yo, we got a friend. A friend.
好的 好的
All right, all right.
我喜歡 我喜歡 知道我什麼意思嗎？我喜歡 好吧
I like it. I like it. You know what I mean? I like it. All right.
- 這是哪兒？- 這裏本來是放熊的
- What is this place? - It's where they kept the bears.
哦 是嗎？好 熊在哪裏？
Oh, yeah? Well, where are the bears?
哦 好 熊 也許我該回去了 弄點東西吃
Yeah, right. Bears. Maybe I should go home, get something to eat.
喂 夥計 嗨 很高興見到你 很漂亮 很漂亮
Oh, hi, fella. Hi, nice to see you. Nice shades. Nice shades.
哦 橋不錯 有點搖
Oh, nice bridge. Little shaky.
嗨 我喜歡這裏 我真的喜歡
Hey, I like this place. I really like it.
- 他的家 - 哦 家 我喜歡 我喜歡
- He's home. - Yeah, home. I like it, I like it.
很多台階 牆上有很多塗畫 像個洞穴
Lot of big steps, lot of graffiti on the wall. A cavelike atmosphere.
就像打火石 福瑞得和維爾馬在哪？
Just like The Flintstones. Where's Fred and Wilma?
- 他很酷 - 你在我的生活裏？
- He's cool. - Where you been all my life?
不是現在 也許以後
Don't get fresh. Maybe later.
我有麻煩
I'm in trouble.
好地方啊 看上去像跳蚤市場 我昨天去購物了
What a place! Looks like a flea market. I went shopping yesterday.
我們是同一個理髮師 你被弄得頭疼？
We got the same barber. You get a headache from that?
沒有比斯麗你會感到非常孤單
You'll be awfully lonely sleeping without Mrs. Beasley.
- 我知道 - 賽得？
- I know. - Zed?
- 我在看家庭時間 - 賽得
- I'm watching Family Affair. - Zed.
是重播 你要什麼？
It's a rerun. What do you want?
- 我想他是個可憐蟲 - 你不認為 弗蘭克 你問啊
- I think he'd be a good Scullion. - You don't think, Flacko. You ask!
- 你叫什麼名字？他們都叫你什麼？- 笨蛋
- You got a name? What do they call you? - Jughead.
笨蛋 我媽媽的名字曾經也叫笨蛋
Jughead. My mother's name was Jughead.
- 我在考慮把他改了 - 為什麼？這是個不錯的美國名字
- Well, I've been thinking of changing it. - Why? It's a good American name.
就像這樣
As such!
好 好 好 耶 好地方 很棒的地方
Right, right, right. Yeah, nice place. Great place.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
曾經有一個女人大概 每星期來一次
I had a woman who used to come in here about once a week...
但是我不得不炒了她 她被淘汰了
but I had to fire her. It didn't pan out.
- 哦 是嗎？我可能知道誰 - 閉嘴
- Oh, really? I might know someone. - Shut up!
- 我誰也不知道 沒有一個人 - 你會緊張什麼？
- I don't know anyone. Not a person. - What are you so nervous about?
我不知道 我不知道 我不知道 這個地方有點神秘
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. The place weirds me out.
聞上去有動物的氣味
It smells like animals.
- 他們帶他去我的地方了？- 噓
- They took him to my place? - Shh!
- 我們在哪裏？- 舊動物園
- Where are we? - The old zoo.
舊動物園
The old zoo!
舊動物園 舊的 不是新的動物園 只是舊的
The old zoo. The old-- Not the new zoo, but the old zoo.
有香煙嗎？抽點煙？
You have a cigarette? Some smokes?
- 老的動物園 - 老的動物園？
- The old zoo. - The old zoo?
- 我從來沒看到過新動物園 - 現在是機會了 斯圖曼
- I never even saw the new zoo. - Well, now's your chance, Schtulman.
盧可能喜歡 像個新家 轉彎
Lou may love it. It'll be like a new home. Turn the wheel!
有光嗎？用不用來點火？
What about a light? What about some little fire?
你不該抽煙 對你的健康不好
You shouldn't smoke. It's bad for your health.
- 想想我要走了 - 星期天 星期天在賽道公園
- Think I'll quit. - At Raceway Park.
- 改裝的高速賽車 - 你很興奮
- Dragsters-- - You're wired!
- 你是個警察 - 不 不 不 我是個歌手
- You're a cop. - No, no, no. I'm a singer.
你是個警察
You're a cop.
你還是個難看的警察
And you're an ugly cop.
所有單位注意 所有單位注意 我們在舊動物園遇到997
Attention all units. Attention all units. We've got a 997 at the old zoo.
- 997？- 我們在舊動物園遇到997
-997? - We got a 997 at the old zoo.
舊動物園遇到997 馬奧尼需要幫助
A 997 at the old zoo. Mahoney needs help.
快點 不是你 盧
Step on it, please. Not you, Lou!
所有單位注意 我們在舊的廢棄的 動物園遇到997
All units. We have a 997 at the old abandoned zoo!
- 你在幹嗎？- 我正在請求增援
- What are you doing? - I was calling for assistance.
- 馬奧尼有麻煩了 - 馬奧尼被停職了
- Mahoney's in trouble. - Mahoney is suspended.
你不會做這種事的
You will do nothing of the kind.
快 快 馬奧尼有麻煩了
Hurry! Hurry! Mahoney's in trouble!
- 馬奧尼 - 快走
- Mahoney! - Let's go!
- 怎麼了？- 馬奧尼有麻煩了
- What's up? - Mahoney's in trouble.
- 我來開車 - 你快上車
- Let me drive. - Will you get in!
嗨 等一下
Hey! Wait a minute!
等一下
Wait a minute!
- 不要讓我發飆啊 - 對不起 賽得 看 放鬆
- Don't make me flare my nostrils! - Excuse me, Zed. Look, relax.
你要冷靜 跟著我呼吸
You gotta calm down. You gotta breathe with me.
- 1 2 3 - 我喝了太多咖啡因
- One, two, three. - I'm getting too much caffeine.
- 嗯 我知道 我要走了 - 我要殺了你
- Yeah, I know. I'm gonna go now. - I ought to kill you!
- 高塔 - 是 長官？
- Hightower. - Yes, sir?
你和瓊斯穿過那座橋
I want you and Jones to cross that bridge.
等在入口處直到聽到我的信號 出發
Wait outside this entrance until you hear my signal. Get going.
別走
No going.
好 好 好
Well, well, well.
如果他不是前隊長
If it isn't the former captain...
皮特 拉賽德
Pete Lassard.
- 你該死的在做什麼？- 我正在計劃攻擊
- What the hell do you think you're doing? - I'm making a plan of attack.
洞的頂上有通風孔 我要從那裏進去
Now, there's an air vent on top of that cave. I'll be going in through there.
- 舒爾曼 - 去你的 這裏我說了算
- Schtulman-- - Like hell you are. I'm in charge here.
- 法克勒 - 是 長官
- Fackler. - Yes, sir.
- 你跟我來 - 去哪？
- You'll come with me. - Where?
去通風孔
To the air vent.
毛瑟上尉
Captain Mauser.
- 安我的辦法來做 - 我不會那開我的肘
- We're gonna do this my way. - I'm not gonna move my elbow.
- 我不要那個 要那個 - 滾出去
- I don't need that. I need that. - Get out of here!
想要交易嗎？
Wanna trade?
好的 你先來 長官
Okay, up you go, sir.
- 把你的手從我的屁股拿開 - 對不起 對不起
- Get your hand out of my ass! - Sorry, sorry.
- 毛瑟 毛瑟 - 毛瑟上尉 過來
- Oh! Mauser! Mauser! - Captain Mauser. Come on.
對不起
Sorry.
- 這是什麼地方？- 熊的洞穴
- What is this place? - Bear cave.
- 過來 - 哦 向橋那裏去
- Come on. - Oh, drawbridge.
- 那是什麼？- 老鼠
- What's that? - Rats.
- 老鼠？- 老鼠
- Rats? - Rats.
好辦法 你呆在這裏 掩護外面
Good idea. You stay here, cover the outside.
馬上回來 我希望
Be right back. I hope.
等等 等等 把蠟燭吹滅
Wait, wait, wait! Blow out the candle.
- 等一下 - 噢
- Wait a minute! - Wow.
回來
Get back!
對不起 我有點緊張 什麼？
Sorry, I'm nervous. What?
把它包在你的腰上 像這樣打2個活結
Wrap it around your waist. Make a double slipknot like this.
- 我會很慢的把你放下去 - 我？
- I'm gonna lower you down real gently. - Me?
不 你媽媽
No, your mother.
- 我告訴你怎麼做 法克勒 - 哦 不
- Let me show you what to do. Fackler! - Oh, no!
哦 媽的
Oh, shit!
- 停下來 - 這是什麼 你們都被捕了
- Stop this thing! - What it is! Everybody's under arrest!
- 他們到了 - 放我出去 法克勒
- They've arrived. - Get me out of here! Fackler!
- 哦 - 放我出去 哦 上帝啊
- Ah! - Get me out of here! Oh, God!
- 賽得 你是通情達理的 - 我討厭這個
- Now, Zed, you're being reasonable. - I hate reasonable!
斯圖曼 是我
Schtulman, it's me!
這裏是警察機關
This is the police department.
扔下武器
Throw down your weapons...
舉起手走出山洞
put up your hands and come out of this cave.
- 嗨 夥計們 - 喔
- Hi, boys. - Whoa.
但是 長官 不
But, sir-- No!
- 賽得 過來 我們談談 - 我沒心情
- Zed, come on, let's talk. - I'm not in the mood!
- 放下槍 - 我有心情
- Drop the gun. - I'm in the mood.
- 你從哪裏來？- 放下槍 阿飛
- So where are you from? - Drop the gun, punk!
你不會開槍的 你沒有子彈
You won't shoot! You don't have any guts!
3秒後 你就沒腦子了
Three more seconds, you don't have any brains.
- 我當然有腦子 - 長官 3秒到了
- I do so have brains. - Sir, three seconds is up.
我大概2個半
I'm on about two and a half!
丟掉
Drop it.
- 幹得好 - 謝謝 馬奧尼 撿起槍
- Good job, sir! - Thanks, Mahoney. Pick up the gun.
那不疼的
That didn't hurt.
- 疼的 - 別動 垃圾帶
- That hurt! - Don't move, dirtbag!
去哪兒 胡克斯？
Where you been, Hooks?
長官 真漂亮啊
Sir, that was beautiful.
從73年來還沒帶過真的彈藥
Haven't carried live ammo since '73.
歡迎回來 隊長
Welcome back, captain.
撲克特
Proctor!
1 2
One. Two.
泰克 你今晚好樣的
Tack. Now, you be a good boy tonight.
你們
You guys.
好了 夥計們 自由了
All right, boys. At ease.
謝謝 還有 哦 不好意思
Thanks. Okay, one more. Oh, excuse me.
- 嗨 司令官 - 馬奧尼 你好嗎？
- Hi, commandant. - Mahoney, how are you?
- 很好 - 我們很想你
- Pretty good. - We've missed you.
- 謝謝 - 沒那麼多
- Thanks. - Not that much.
- 再見 - 再見
- Bye! - Bye-bye!
再見
Bye!